leonisa.com 2013-08-20

# Privacy Policy | Leonisa

Leonisa is committed to respect the privacy rights of all the site users and of the clients who register in this website. These policies describe how Leonisa collects, protects and uses the information received.

## Privacy Policy 

Leonisa will not retain any of its clients’ personal information (name, address, phone, email) unless it is voluntarily released. If you want to register to get an account in our webpage, we will ask for personal information (name, address, email, phone, etc.) This information will be stored in your personal account. Once you are registered, you will be able to purchase in our webpage. When you make a purchase in Leonisa, we will ask for your credit card number, your billing address and your shipping address. We will send you a confirmation email as soon as you get registered or make a payment. 

We will retain some of your personal information to get to know your needs and likes. This will help us to enhance our products and better serve you. It is also possible that Leonisa saves some information about your previous purchases so we can customize our page according to your specific needs. We will send you information related to our products and special offers via email. If you want to stop receiving our emails, you will be able to do so, by sending an email to infousa@leonisa.com. Please keep in mind that if you make a future purchase we will have to retain your information to verify your billing and shipping addresses.

## Children

Leonisa’s webpage does not intend to collect any information from children younger than 16 years old. If for any reason some parents or guardians have provided us children information, they should send us an email to infousa@leonisa.com letting us know that we need to remove the child’s information

## Cookies

When you get into Leonisa’s webpage, some information will be downloaded in your computer as “cookies” or similar files. “Cookies” enable, among other things, our webpage and our advertising to be customized according to the needs and wants of our customers. Cookies are not harmful. These files will not damage your computers and your personal information can not be retrieved through “cookies.” 

If you want to disable “cookies”, most web browsers will let you erase them from your computer’s hard drive. You can also prevent “cookies” from being stored and you will receive a signal before “cookies” are downloaded. You should read your web browser’s instructions in order to learn more about these functions. 

## Safety

Your information’s safety is very important for Leonisa. Because of our supreme technology we can guarantee that your personal information will be protected on the sending and storage process throughout Secure Socket Layer (SSL). We also use Digital Secure Server Identification in order to provide you with the best Internet protection technology. Our database is securely stored and protected against non-authorized access.

There is not 100% secure information in the Internet. This is why we can not guarantee that your personal information will be completely safe. Nevertheless Leonisa will always try to protect your personal information using all the possible methods known to us. You have to take into account that keeping your user name and password and any other personal information secret, is your responsibility.

## Links

We can not certify that the personal information that you send to other web pages linked to ours will be protected. These external web pages are just linked to ours, but operate independently.

## Terms Acceptance

By using this webpage it is implied that you agree with our Safety and Privacy Terms. If you do not agree with any of these terms, please do not use Leonisa’s web site. Leonisa has the right to change these terms, so you must check them constantly. If you keep using Leonisa’s web site, you are implying that you accept our Safety and Privacy terms. For more information please contact us at infousa@leonisa.com
